Go and pick out some bread and drinks for breakfast tomorrow.
Right!
You don't need to run!
He doesn't listen to a word people say...
Hm... What do we need for a cold? Water, sports drinks...
Dairy products and the like...
Maybe some food that's easy on the stomach...
Should we buy something for you to have for breakfast, too?
Cereal or something?
Yeah...
Daikichi...
Did she catch it from me?
Rin...
There are cold germs floating around all the time.
Sometimes people catch it, and sometimes they don't.
There's no point worrying about who caught what from whom.
Can I pick something to take with us when we go to see her?
Sure.
This.
Put it in the basket.
Ah, Kouki-kun!
What're you doing in the sweets aisle?!
Kouki! I told you to get something for breakfast!
It came out!
Usagi
Drop
I can't tell what'll come tomorrow.
ashita no koto wa wakaranai
明日のことはわからない
This is different than making a sacrifice.
kore tte gisei to wa chigau
これって犠牲とは違う
Something about it is different.
nanika ga chigau
何かが違う
And I don't think of it as some sort of forfeit.
batsu geemu ja nante omowanai
罰ゲームじゃなんて思わない
So I just don't get why.
...tte nande na no ka wakaranai
...ってなんでなのか分からない
I can't quite wrap my head around it,
chotto shakuzen to shinai kedo
ちょっと釈然としないけど
but your existence is now much more than just important to me.
kimi no sonzai ima daiji da nante mon ja nai
君の存在今大事だなんてもんじゃない
There's nothing in this world that doesn't come to an end.
owaranai koto nante kono yo no doko ni mo nai
終わらないことなんてこの世のどこにもない
I don't cry because I'm hurting.
naku no wa tsurain ja nai no
泣くのは辛いんじゃないの
They're the sweet, sweet drops of love!
ai no sweet drops sweet drops
愛の sweet drops sweet drops
I want to go on dreaming forever, you know?
zutto yume mite mitai ne
ずっと夢見てみたいね
I want to try and be more gentle, you know?
motto yasashiku shitai ne
もっと優しくしたいね
If I can be with you, I'm happy.
kimi to iraretara happy
君といられたらhappy
Girls are really strong, aren't they?
onna no ko tte tsuyoi ne
女の子って強いね
But sometimes, they can be really weak, you know?
dakedo tokidoki yowai ne
だけど時々弱いね
Our wishes are happy, happy, happy.
bokura no negai wa happy happy happy
僕らの願いは happy happy happy
And our days will be just as happy!
sonna hibi mo happy
そんな日々も happy
Just wanna make you happy!
This is my place!
We probably shouldn't go in, after all.
It'll just be an extra worry for your mum.
Okay.
The food's in here, so you can give it to her.
It's heavy.
Heavy!
Let's go, Rin.
Yeah.
Mum! Daikichi brought us food!
Listen to what people say, already!
Hey, Kouki...
Daikichi-san...
Thank you so much. You've done so much for us.
No, I should be thanking you after all you did for Rin...
How is she?
She's much better now.
She went back to school today, too.
Good evening...
Good evening. It's good that you're all better, Rin-chan.
Yeah...
I'm cooking up some of that rice porridge right now,
so I'll be better in no time.
Right!
Rin! Let's go throw my tooth!
This way!
Be careful, Kouki!
I know!
Nitani-san, you might have caught
this because you watched over Rin.
I'm really sorry.
We'll throw it from here, okay?
I come into contact with countless people each day.
We're so high up...
I'm going to throw it onto that roof!
Every day I ride a packed train to the office.
There's no guarantee it came from her, right?
So don't worry about it.
It's just a cold.
I see.
Well, at least let me help with Kouki,
even if it's just picking him up and bringing him home.
Thank you so much...
Rin, we're going now.
Daikichi, let's play video games!
Sure thing, next time I'm here.
Kouki... Make sure and help your mum, okay?
Okay.
Oh, right.
The pudding and the smaller drink are from Rin.
Thank you, Rin-chan!
Pudding is my favourite!
Good night.
Daikichi! Hurry up!
Why are you up so early? It's Sunday!
I already told you! We're practising for the skipping competition!
Oh, yeah.
What's wrong?
This one's wobbly, too.
Brush slowly.
Right...
Stop wiggling it!
Okay...
Ouch!
You shouldn't be pushing yourself so hard yet.
Oh, no. I'm fine now.
I'm sorry for always taking advantage of your kindness.
I think I'm the one who should be saying that.
Thank you so much.
Not at all.
I'm surprised Kouki's having such trouble.
He just can't seem to get it right.
Kouki, you're jumping too early.
The jump rope whirls around like this, so you should be jumping here, right?
Yeah...
So why are you moving your legs and arms at the same time?
Oh, I see...
Your move your arms first, and then your legs.
First, try it slowly once.
Got it!
Daikichi! Me, too! Me, too!
Right, right...
Your problem is that you're swinging
your arms in circles that are too big, Rin.
Keep your arms in like this.
Daikichi-san!
Oh!
You're early!
Good morning!
I don't see why they're so fired up...
Nobu-kun's really good!
It's because he has a big brother.
He has someone to learn everything from.
Huh...
You don't want to join in, Sayaka-chan?
She just lost one of her upper teeth, so...
It's hard being a girl, huh? Even as a kid...
Sayaka-chan... What sort of container do you hold your teeth in?
Did your parents get you a cute one?
What do you mean?
Don't you know? There are cases that you can
put your kid's old baby teeth in as a memento.
A memento?
They have these tiny cute ones.
Tiny!
Cute!
Right?
Yeah! Mine's a butterfly!
I bought one for Kouki, too, but he doesn't save his teeth.
Rin would love one of those!
I'm an idiot! I should've known there'd be something like that!
Since I've met Rin, every day's been like this,
freaking out and fussing over the tiniest things.
Daikichi, this is for you!
I drew it in school!
Daikichi makes really good beef
and potatoes. And he can run fast.
Daikichi
I had to write about a member of my family.
I guess it's fine...
It's so cute!
What is this?
You put your baby teeth in it when they fall out.
As a little keepsake.
A keepsake?
Thank you, Kouki-kun's mum!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
But isn't that Kouki's?
It's fine. It's fine...
I throw mine!
Well, yes...
I've thrown all of mine on the roof until now.
Is that okay?
It's fine.
You can throw them or keep them. It's up to you!
Oh, right.
Rin. I'm going to give skipping my all next time, too!
You're poking at your tooth again...
If you leave it alone, it'll come out on its own.
Though, either way, she's going to look like someone punched her lights out.
She won't be able to smile, at the very least...
There, done.
Right. Let's go!
Have you grown taller again?
Huh? You're going to do it, too, Daikichi-san?
I'm starting to pick up a little excess weight.
Me, too!
It's tough when you get older, huh?
I've got to nip it in the bud, somehow.
Daikichi-san's doing it like a boxer!
That's amazing!
This is easier on your knees.
Huh...
Daikichi! Teach me how to do that, too!
Forget it!
No fair! How come only you get to look cool?
You have to learn to do it normally first!
What?!
Hey, wait!
Me, too! Me, too!
Rin-chan! You can do it backwards! That's amazing!
Kids sure are amazing...
Huh, is it really?
They have so much energy, haven't they?
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
I don't know where they get it from.
One more time!
Though, adults are pretty amazing, too.
Adults?
I'm sure you already know, but I'm not Rin's dad.
We only started living together a year ago.
Before that, I spent all of my time just thinking about myself,
but once I met her, my whole lifestyle changed.
You guys have been with your kids their whole lives.
I'm still pretty new to this, so it's not really a big deal yet,
but I'm wondering if it's really possible to deal with...
...never having any real alone time again.
I don't mind it at all!
Me neither.
Huh? Really?
Well, you know...
What? What?!
Hey, Rin... Wasn't today the skipping competition?
Rin...
I messed up...
How many skips did you do?
Fifteen.
That's terri-
What about backwards?
Two hundred and three!
What?!
You can do that many?!
I guess that got you... first place?
Yeah.
Here's the certificate.
Certificate of Achievement
First year group
Backwards Jump 1st place
Kaga Rin
You sure did well! This is amazing.
But I could've done way better on forward jumping...
Well, you did only get one chance.
Yeah...
And you're really good at it now.
I know that, even if they don't.
Yeah.
I lost weight!
Huh?
Hey!
Are we almost there?
Hm... About ten more minutes.
They'll want to see that wobbly tooth of yours.
Yeah!
I keep telling you not to touch it unless you need to...
And I'll show them my skipping, too!
Right!
You've grown so much recently.
I'm sure Mum and Dad are going to get a shock!
I wonder if I'm taller than Auntie now?
I don't think you've grown that much...
We have to go and fill Granddad in on things, too.
Yeah.
We're here!
Oh, Rin-chan! I've been waiting for you!
Hello.
You've grown so big!
Are you one of the the biggest in your class?
Yeah!
You should have called! I would have come to the station.
Rin is capable of walking for ten minutes, you know...
You're going to be taller than me soon!
Ah! Kazumi-oneechan!
Yo. You're here early.
Yeah. I arrived a while before you.
Those clothes...
They were yours, right?
Yeah...
Auntie sent them to me a while ago!
Rin-chan, let me see your teeth.
Okay!
Two of the front teeth are wobbly just now!
Are you okay? It doesn't hurt, does it?
It hurts a little sometimes, but I'm used to it.
I'm a pro!
Hey, Daikichi!
Can't you do anything to help her?!
Her gums are all red!
It's just a little swelling.
Besides, when I was younger, you said you'd pull mine out with thread!
With thread?
My! I don't quite remember...
I tried to make everything easy to chew.
Thank you!
Want some freeze-dried tofu?
Yeah!
Can I have some beans, too, Auntie?
Of course!
You just eat up, okay?
I love freeze-dried tofu!
Did it fall out?
Rin-chan...
It came out!
Blood! Blood!
Mum! A tissue! A tissue!
Wait! Wait!
I'm fine!
Rin, use this for now!
That's a dust cloth!
Rin-chan has changed so much.
I wonder...
Maybe she's always been like that on the inside...
Hm...
So you're getting married, huh?
Mum told me earlier.
Yeah.
That's nice. She said that he seemed like a good guy.
Yeah, I guess...
The only problem is that he wants kids straight away...
What's wrong with that?
Are you kidding me?!
No going out drinking. No concerts.
No holidays. No good food.
I wouldn't be able to do anything anymore!
I think you should be talking to him about this.
There's not much I can say...
I'm not even into kids to begin with.
And I don't want to become one of those obnoxious mums!
I don't think I could sacrifice myself just to raise a kid...
Nah, I think you'd make it work.
If you really wanted to.
I guess when the kid's already there, you don't really have a choice.
That's easy for you to say...
Yeah, maybe...
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know what it's like to be a husband. Nor a father. Nor a mother, of course.
It's burning.
Yeah...
I might not have time to go shopping or sit around drinking tea,
but my time at work is my own.
And my time with my son is my own, too.
All of it is precious to me.
I don't think there's any special trick to being a parent.
Heck, the world's full of people just like us!
I see...
I guess so, huh?
Hey, Granddad...
My adult teeth are starting to come in.
Hey! Rin!
T-This is sweat!
Daikichi!
Hurry up!
Say, "Cheese!"
That vase...
Masako-san had one just like it.
I'll be right back!
Daikichi!
What?! The other one feels like it's going to come out?!
Mirror! Mirror!
I'm sure that I'll go on fussing and worrying over the smallest things...
Though that's probably true of all of us.
Does it hurt?
Rin!
Daikichi, look!
What the heck? You look like a cat!
I know, right?
Send a text to your parents!
A photo?
Whatever else happens,
I feel like I'll go on being happy when I see her smile.
Hurry up!
Right! Open your mouth!
And I think things are just fine like that.
A sunny Sunday's early afternoon;
nichiyou no hareta hirusagari
日曜の晴れた昼下がり
where should we go today?
kyou wa doko e yukou?
今日はどこへ行こう？
The same old road that I'm so used to walking on...
kayoinareta itsumo no michi ga
通い慣れたいつもの道が
...shines with a dazzling light.
mabushiku kagayaite mieru
眩しく 輝いて見える
If I have the warm sunlight shining down on me...
terasu atatakai taiyou to
照らす暖かい太陽と
...and you by my side...
tonari ni kimi ga ireba...
隣に君がいれば
Whoa! High, high, high!
My feelings are ready to burst forth.
hashagidasu kimochi ni
はしゃぎだす気持ちに
Sing out, lai lai lai!
utae lai lai lai!
歌え lai lai lai!
My voice reaches every corner of the earth.
koe wa doko made mo
声はどこまでも
I'm already high, high, high!
mou high high high!
もう high high high!
Riding the whirling winds...
maiagaru kaze ni nori
舞い上がる風に乗り
Sing out, lai lai lai!
utae lai lai lai!
歌え lai lai lai!
My voice swoops up and down with me.
koe mo tobihaneru
声も飛び跳ねる
Daikichi!